const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'When was Ableton Live first released?',
        answers: ['1998', '1993', '2004', '2001'],
        correct: '2001'
    },     
    {
        question: "What is the name of Ableton Live's parametric equalizer?",
        answers: ['ParaEQ', 'EQ Three', 'EQ Eight', 'Equalizer'],
        correct: 'EQ Eight'
    },
    {
        question: 'In music production, changing the value of a parameter over time is called...?',
        answers: ['Modulation', 'Automation', 'Parameterization', 'Novation'],
        correct: 'Automation'
    },
    {
        question: 'Sidechain compression can be achieved on which of the below Ableton Live devices?',
        answers: ['Compressor', 'Glue Compressor', 'Multiband Compressor', 'All of the Above'],
        correct: 'All of the Above'
    },
    {
        question: 'Ableton Live was initially created as an instrument. What is the name of the view that this refers to?',
        answers: ['Session View', 'Arrangement View', 'Player View', 'Timeline View'], 
        correct: 'Session View'
    },
    {
        question: 'What does MIDI stand for?',
        answers: ['-Music Indication Delimiter Interface', 'Multi-Instrumental Delivery Instruction', 'Musical Instrument Digitial Interface', 'Markup Inductor Display Infrastructur'],
        correct: 'Musical Instrument Digitial Interface'
    },
    {
        question: 'Ableton has released a hardware device to augment Live. What is it called?',
        answers: ['-Push', 'Hotpads', 'Sing', 'Launchpad'],
        correct: 'Push'
    },
    {
        question: 'What programming language is Ableton Live written in?',
        answers: ['Python', 'Java', 'Perl', 'C++'],
        correct: 'C++'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the visual coding language that Ableton Live devices are written in?',
        answers: ['Cycling74', 'Max', 'Moop', 'MLI'],
        correct: 'Max'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the new wavetable synth included in Ableton Live 10?',
        answers: ['Wave', 'FM', 'Wavetable', 'Inductor'],
        correct: 'Wavetable'
    },
];